<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://localhost:4000/assets/xslt/rss.xslt" ?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/css" href="http://localhost:4000/assets/css/rss.css" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
	<channel>
		<title>Han Group at SJTU</title>
		<description>Ke Han research group at Shanghai Jiao Tong University. We work on neutrinoless double beta decay, dark matter WIMP search, and other rare event/particle searches.</description>
		<link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
		<atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
		
			<item>
				<title>Professor Yannis K. Semertzidis</title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/seminar/visitor/</link>
				<pubDate>Tue, 09 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;Director of Center for Axion and Precision Physics, IBS
   Korea Advanced Inst of Science and Technology (KAIST)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Room 3304, E6-2 Natural Science Building 
   291 Daehak-ro, (373-1 Guseong-dong) Yuseong-gu, Daejeon 305-701
   Republic of Korea
   Phone: +82-42-350-2522 / Fax: +82-42-350-2510 / yannis@kaist.ac.kr 
    http://capp.ibs.re.kr/html/capp_en&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/seminar/visitor/</guid>
			</item>
		
			<item>
				<title>Ke joins SJTU </title>
				<link>http://localhost:4000/announcement/KeHan/</link>
				<pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2016 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
				<description>&lt;p&gt;My current research focuses on exploring fundamental properties of neutrinos, specifically the nature of neutrinos, the origin of its mass, and the total number of flavors. I have been a member of the CUORE experiment to search for neutrinoless double-beta decay of Te-130 with a large bolometer array. Since 2013, I have been working a Physics Coordinator to oversee data analysis, simulation, and computing effort of the collaboration. More recently I started working on the PROSPECT project to search for sterile neutrinos and measure reactor neutrino spectrum precisely. I am a founding member of the collaboration and leading the design of photo multiplier tube assembly. I am also especially interested in characterizing liquid scintillator response to positrons and collaborating with the beam physics lab here to develop a tunable mono-energetic positron beam for detector calibration.
&lt;!--more--&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3&gt;Collaborations:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt; 
    * 2009 - present: CUORE (Neutrinoless double-beta decay of Te-130)
        -  Elected senior Physics Coordinator; Oversee data analysis, simulation, and computing effort of the collaboration.
        - Led data analyses of neutrinoless double-beta decay search in CUORE-0 (published recently in Physical Review Letters). 
        - Detector R&amp;amp;D and radioactive background mitigation. 
     
    * 2014 - present: PROSPECT (Sterile neutrino search)
        - Detector development. 
        - Optical simulation to optimize light collection of PROSPECT detectors.
        - Proposed  to study non-linearity of  scintillator light yield using  a Compton spectrometer; Supervising students to set up the spectrometer.
        - Constructing a tunable mono-energetic positron beam to calibrate  PROSPECT detectors (in collaboration with the Beam Physics group at Yale).
     
    * 2009 - 2012: KamLAND (reactor neutrino experiment)
        - Studied and improved the linearity of energy and vertex reconstruction algorithm of the KamLAND detector.
        - Participated the full volume energy calibration of KamLAND
     
    * 2004 - 2009: LSSS (Lunar Soil Strangelet Search: search for stable strangelet in lunar soil using the accelerator mass spectrometry technique)
        - PhD thesis project. Published in PRL | (PRL Synopsis: Strangelets in the night).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 class=&quot;t60&quot; id=&quot;other-post-formats&quot;&gt;Other Post Formats&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul class=&quot;side-nav&quot;&gt;

  

    
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://localhost:4000/seminar/visitor/&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Professor Yannis K. Semertzidis&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    

  
&lt;/ul&gt;

</description>
				<guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/announcement/KeHan/</guid>
			</item>
		
	</channel>
</rss>
